(this.webpackJsonpquiz2=this.webpackJsonpquiz2||[]).push([[0],[,,function(t){t.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"Which is the only mammal that can\u2019t jump?","optionA":"Dog","optionB":"Elephant","optionC":"Goat","optionD":"Lion","answer":"Elephant"},{"question":"The largest country in the world is","optionA":"The United States","optionB":"India","optionC":"Japan","optionD":"Russia","answer":"Russia"},{"question":"The largest river in the world is","optionA":"Nile","optionB":"Ganga","optionC":"Amazon","optionD":"Yangtze","answer":"Nile"},{"question":"The Largest Desert in the World","optionA":"Sahara","optionB":"Taar","optionC":"Antartic","optionD":"Arabian","answer":"Antartic"},{"question":"The Largest Continent in the World","optionA":"Africa","optionB":"Asia","optionC":"Europe","optionD":"North America","answer":"Asia"},{"question":"The Largest Airport in the World","optionA":"Beijing Airport","optionB":"Los Angeles Airport","optionC":"Atlanta Airport","optionD":"Tokyo Airport","answer":"Atlanta Airport"},{"question":"The Largest Ocean in the World","optionA":"Atlantic Ocean","optionB":"Indian Ocean","optionC":"Pacific Ocean","optionD":"Southern Ocean","answer":"Pacific Ocean"},{"question":"The Largest Animal in the World","optionA":"Elephant","optionB":"Whale","optionC":"Girafee","optionD":"Camel","answer":"Whale"},{"question":"Which is the Capital of India","optionA":"Delhi","optionB":"TamilNadu","optionC":"AndraPradesh","optionD":"Maharastra","answer":"Delhi"},{"question":"Where is Gateway of India Located","optionA":"Mumbai","optionB":"Chennai","optionC":"Delhi","optionD":"Kolkata","answer":"Mumbai"},{"question":"Who is the current World Champion in MotoGp","optionA":"Marc Marques","optionB":"Valentino Rossi","optionC":"John Mir","optionD":"Dani Pedrosa","answer":"John Mir"},{"question":"Which cricketer is know as Master-Blaster","optionA":"Rohit Sharma","optionB":"Virat Kohli","optionC":"MS Dhoni","optionD":"Sachin Tendulkar","answer":"Sachin Tendulkar"},{"question":"Who lifted the Cricket World Cup in 2011","optionA":"India","optionB":"Australia","optionC":"South Africa","optionD":"New Zealand","answer":"India"},{"question":"Which country has powerfull army force in the world","optionA":"India","optionB":"China","optionC":"U.S","optionD":"Russia","answer":"U.S"},{"question":"Which stadium is Considered as World;s Largest in the World","optionA":"Motera Stadium","optionB":"Wankadae Stadium","optionC":"MA Chidambaram Stadium","optionD":"Eden Garden Stadium","answer":"Motera Stadium"}]')},,,,,,,,,,,function(t,n,i){},function(t,n,i){},,function(t,n,i){},function(t,n,i){"use strict";i.r(n);var o=i(1),e=i.n(o),a=i(4),s=i.n(a),r=(i(13),i(5)),c=i(6),p=i(8),h=i(7),l=(i(14),i(2)),u=i(0),d=0,j=function(t){Object(p.a)(i,t);var n=Object(h.a)(i);function i(){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(t=n.call(this)).next=function(){d+=1,t.setState({details:l[d]})},t.previous=function(){d-=1,t.setState({details:l[d]})},t.quit=function(){document.getElementById("container").style.display="none"},t.state={details:l[d]},t}return Object(c.a)(i,[{key:"render",value:function(){return console.log(l),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{id:"container",className:"contain",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(u.jsx)("div",{children:"Question"}),Object(u.jsxs)("pre",{children:[Object(u.jsxs)("span",{children:["  ",d+1," of 15"]}),Object(u.jsx)("span",{className:"question",children:this.state.details.question})]})]}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:[Object(u.jsx)("button",{children:this.state.details.optionA}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{children:this.state.details.optionB}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{children:this.state.details.optionC}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{children:this.state.details.optionD})]}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"buttons-section",children:[Object(u.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.previous,children:"Previous"}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.next,children:"Next"}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.quit,children:"Quit"})]})]})}}]),i}(e.a.Component);i(16);var A=function(){return Object(u.jsx)(j,{})},b=function(t){t&&t instanceof Function&&i.e(3).then(i.bind(null,18)).then((function(n){var i=n.getCLS,o=n.getFID,e=n.getFCP,a=n.getLCP,s=n.getTTFB;i(t),o(t),e(t),a(t),s(t)}))};s.a.render(Object(u.jsx)(e.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(u.jsx)(A,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),b()}],[[17,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.391bb46d.chunk.js.map